桑蒂诺军事学院  始建于1841年
堆书可控  高效节能
Control stacked, energy-efficient.
话说  全部馆藏估计
Now, mind you, the whole
一个电子阅读器就能装下
collection could probably fit on a Kindle,
至少下雨时学员们
but at least the cadets will have
又多了个地方躲雨
another placeto get out of the rain.
你对图书馆设计提意见了吗
Did you have any input on the design?
我核准了蓝图
I approved the blueprints.
如果要把我的名字留在上面
If something's gonna have my name on it,
我得保证那东西建得没什么问题
I want to make damn sure they build it right.
我丈夫是把他自己当成建筑师了
I think my husband fancies himself a bit of an architect.
杰弗逊就设计了蒙蒂塞洛庄园
Well, Jefferson designed Monticello.
他还跟自己的奴隶乱搞
And he also fucked his slaves.
幸好我没有奴隶
Luckily, I don't have any,
所以我从没受到过这种诱惑
so that particular temptation hasn't presented itself.
桑蒂诺[哨兵]学院
The Sentinel...
南卡罗莱纳最好的军事院校
South Carolina's premiere military college.
我在这儿学到了荣誉  职责和尊重的价值
They taught me the values of honor, duty, and respect.
也曾受到戏弄和打击
They also hazed me, tried to break me,
大四时险遭开除
and, senior year, nearly expelled me
那年我志愿参与参议员竞选  致使学业荒废
when I volunteered for a Senate Race and my studies suffered.
但30年后  他们还是为新建一座图书馆
But that didn't stop them from soliciting a hefty sum
向我要了一笔巨款
for their new library 30 years later.
在权力和财富的笼罩下
How quickly poor grades
糟糕的成绩就这样被甩在脑后
are forgotten in the shadow of power and wealth.
你这酒杯才一半满嘛  弗兰克
Your drink is only about half as full as it should be, Frank.
你想把我灌醉吗
Are you trying to get me drunk?
灌醉  昏倒在水沟里
Drunk, passed out in the gutter,
这样我就能把你妻子偷走了
so I can steal your wife.
你收到邀请步枪手的邮件了吗
Did you get the email about the riflemen?
-什么邮件  -发自我办公室的邀请邮件
- What email? - From my office about the invitations.
我还希望能见着他们呢
I was hoping they would be here.
我去查下客人名单
I'll check the list,
但我不记得收过这样的邮件啊
but I don't remember any email.
没关系  只是问一下罢了
Oh, not a problem. I was just wondering.
真是的  弗兰克  太抱歉了
Well, shit, Frank, I'm sorry.
千万别上火
Don't you sweat it for a second.
这样吧  你给我倒点酒  就算补偿我了
In fact, here's how you can make it up to me... freshen my drink.
没问题
That I can do.
祝贺你  议员先生
Congratulations, Congressman.
雷米  很高兴在这儿见到你
Remy. Nice to see you here.
格里和桑科的所有同僚都向你问好
Gerry and all the folks at Sancorp give you their regards.
很遗憾他们不能亲临现场
Well, I'm sorry they couldn't make it.
克莱尔在哪
Where's Claire?
她一定在哪里婉拒仰慕者呢
Oh, she's here somewhere, fending off admirers.
桑科对她回绝了他们的捐款感到非常失望
Sancorp was very disappointed she turned down their donation.
不难想象
I can imagine.
他们还很关心
And they're also concerned
彼得・罗素竞选州长一事
about Peter Russo running for Governor.
你怎么知道的
Now, how do you know about that?
宾州有四分之三的土地
Three quarters of Pennsylvania
下面有页岩天然气田
sits on top of the Marcellus Shale.
我连谁在竞选州长都不知道
If I can't find out who's running for governor,
那我就配不上他们给的酬劳了
I don't deserve a dime of what they're paying me.
弗兰西斯・J・安德伍德议员图书馆
罗素发起的流域法案
This watershed bill Russo sponsors
对天然气开采有很多限制
places a lot of restrictions on drilling.
雷米  国会在休息
Remy, congress is in recess,
这个周末不要谈工作
and this weekend is not about work.
抱歉  你说得很对
I apologize. You are absolutely right.
桑科是你唯一的客户吗
Is Sancorp your only account?
还有不少
I have plenty.
但其他客户不会为你的图书馆
But my other clients didn't pay for your library
和我来这儿的机票买单
or my plane ticket down here.
对你来说正好旅游了
It's a nice little junket for you.
真心希望你能去看看风景
I do hope you're taking in the sights.
这不是我第一次来查尔斯顿了
This isn't my first trip to Charleston.
不是作为我的新闻发言人肯定是第一次
But I'll bet it's your first time not as my press secretary.
没错
It is.
你还邀请了谁
Who else do you have coming in?
我不想请太多人
I didn't want to pack tonight too much.
要知道  这种宴会通常只招待有钱人
You know, these receptions are usually just for the money people
比如你
like yourself.
通常来说  现在我该开始絮叨
Normally, this is where I would start to drone on
桑蒂诺学院的历史  理念
about the Sentinel's history, its philosophy,
之类的
its yadda, yadda, yadda.
但我决定明天正式演讲时再讲这些
But I'm going to save that for my big speech tomorrow,
这样你们就不用受两次折磨
and that way I'm not gonna bore y'all to tears twice.
今晚我们要把时间留给
Tonight we're going to turn it over
一位大家很熟悉的人
to a man who needs no introduction,
我们都清楚他是怎样一个混蛋
because we all know what a son of a bitch he is.
言归正传
Seriously, though,
弗兰克・安德伍德诠释了
Frank Underwood exemplifies
我们努力灌输给学生的所有美德
all the virtues we try to instill in our graduates.
我们很自豪拥有你样的校友  弗兰克
We're so proud to call you an alumnus, Frank,
更自豪将你的名字永远留在校园里
and to have your name as a permanent fixture on our campus.
有请国会议员弗兰克・安德伍德
Congressman Frank Underwood!
谢谢你  希金斯校长
Thank you, president Higgins.
我首先要感谢桑科工业
I first want to thank Sancorp Industries
为新建图书馆提供资金
for providing the funds to make the library possible.
我刚成为这里的学员时
When I matriculated here as a young cadet,
吉米・卡特刚当选总统
Jimmy Carter had just been elected president.
毕业以后
After I graduated,
我真希望自己还能待四年
I wished that I could have had another four years,
吉米也是
just like Jimmy.
可惜我们都未能如愿
Well, neither of us got our wish.
但我带着愉快的记忆离开了校园
But I left this campus with fond memories.
我第一次...
The first time I ever...
噢  多希望我在棉花之地*
*Oh, I wish I was in the land of cotton
旧时光难以忘怀*
*Old times there are not forgotten
看吧  看吧  看吧*
*Look away, look away, look away
我收到你的邮件了
I got your damn email.
多希望我在迪克西*
*I wish I was in Dixie
万岁  万岁*
*Hooray, hooray
在迪克西  我会表明立场*
*In dixieland, I'll take my stand
生于迪克西  死于迪克西*
*To live and die in Dixie
走吧  走吧*
*Away, away
一路向南去迪克西*
*Away down South in Dixie
走吧  走吧*
*Away, away
一路向南去迪克西*
*Away down South in Dixie
穿过蒙特祖玛的长廊*
*From the halls of Montezuma
去往的黎波里的海岸*
*To the shores of Tripoli
我们将为国而战*
*We will fight our country's battles
宝贝孩子
the honey child...
当她走向...
when she stepped out in the...
在《亚特兰大的主妇》里穿上胸罩
trying on the bra on housewives of Atlanta,
我取笑你来着
and I teased you about that,
我说...我叫它宝贝孩子
and I said... I called it the honey child,
因为她就是个宝贝孩子嘛
because she's the honey child now.
总之  问题是...
Anyway, here's the thing...
灯像这样多久了
How long has that light been like that?
不知道  大概一个月吧
I don't know. A month, maybe.
没人来修吗
And nobody's come to fix it?
这里没人修任何东西
Nobody don't fix nothing around here.
你问了吗
Well, have you asked?
嘘  我在看电视
Shh. I'm watching.
别管它  我都习惯了
Leave it alone. I'm used to it now.
好多了吧
Better, huh?
现在太暗了
Now it's too dark.
你这是干什么
What did you do that for?
听我说  妈  我要竞选州长
Listen, ma, I'm running for Governor.
再过几天我就要宣布了
I'm going to announce it in a few days.
所以我才来费城
That's why I came up to Philly.
明天有个社区会议
There's a community meeting tomorrow.
我要向船厂的人介绍一个计划
I'm going to talk to the shipbuilders about a plan
让他们重新找到工作
to bring their jobs back
这样他们就会在竞选中支持我
so they'll support me in the election.
这些事我一窍不通
I don't know nothing about that stuff.
我听不懂
It's over my head.
好  听我说  你会在新闻里看到
Okay, listen, there's going to be some stories
一些关于我的事
coming out about me in the news...
我的过去
about my past.
我只想给你提个醒
I just wanted to give you a heads-up
让你有个准备
so it doesn't catch you off guard.
我早就不看新闻了  全是垃圾
I don't watch the news no more. A bunch of garbage.
你想看看凯文和萨拉的照片吗
You want to see some pictures of Kevin and Sarah?
太暗了看不清
Too dark to look at pictures.
不不  照片在我手机里  不用...
No, no, no. It's on my phone. You don't need any...
拿远点  我讨厌那些东西
Get it away from me. I hate those things.
会致癌的
Brain cancer.
我是个匠人  有把热胶枪
I'm a crafter, and I have a hot glue gun,
我很会...
and I can very well do this my...
可不仅是在楼上
It wasn't just up the stairs,
要往上走三段楼梯呢
it was up three flights of stairs,
科学馆里面啊
in the science building.
格肯海默怎么说的来着
And Guckenheimer, what did he did...
"您今天美极了  州长夫人"
"Well, you look lovely today, Mrs. Governor."
然后那畜生竟然大便了
And the thing took a dump.
没错  他们后来一直没能要回来...
Right. And they couldn't get it back...
牵头牛上三段楼容易
You can get a cow up three flights of stairs,
牵下来就难了
but you can't get it down.
所以安迪才问
And that's why Andy said...
"晚餐想吃牛排吗"
"Who wants steak for dinner?"
-聊得怎么样  -高兴极了
- How are you boys doing? - We're good.
-你觉得我胖吗  -别理他
- You think I'm fat? - Take the Fifth.
我说真的  菲尔说我是老来发福
Seriously, Phil, here, thinks I got fat with old age.
那是宰相肚里能撑船
Ah, you're a big man with an even bigger heart.
听到了吧
There you go.
她是说你很丰满
She said you're chubby.
弗兰克  我先回酒店了
Frank, I'm going to go back to the hotel.
玩得开心点
Okay? Have fun.
-我爱这女人  -是啊
- I love this woman. - Yeah, she...
可别让他捅娄子
Don't let him get into too much trouble.
和我们几个鬼混一晚
They'll have grounds for impeachment
他就该被弹劾了
when we're done with him.
趁他们没关张再去弄点酒吧
Better get another drink before they close up.
你跟我去搬
You're coming with me to help carry them.
今晚你就是侍应生了
You're gonna be a waiter tonight.
真是懒鬼学员  懒鬼学员
Lazy-ass cadet. Lazy-ass cadet.
兄弟  等一下
Yeah, hold on a second there, partner.
你完全不知道我们会来吗
You had no idea we were coming?
完全是个惊喜
Complete surprise.
我还以为希金斯会
I thought Higgins might have...
没有  他装得可像了
No, he played it perfectly.
让我以为你们压根不会来
Made me think you weren't coming at all.
开玩笑吧  我们绝对不会错过的
Are you kidding? We wouldn't have missed it for the world.
图书馆上是写"弗兰克"还是"弗兰西斯"
On the library, are they going to put "Frank" Or "Francis"?
"弗兰西斯"  和我国会大厦
Francis. It's the same as the name
办公室门上的铭牌一致
above the door in my office in the Capitol.
"弗兰西斯"确实更适合命名图书馆
"Francis" is better for libraries.
"弗兰克"更适合作宣传贴纸
"Frank" is better for bumper stickers.
我还真那么干过
I got a few of those.
还有人喊你弗兰西斯吗
Does anybody ever actually call you Francis?
只有克莱尔这么叫我
Claire does. She's the only one.
她真是位难得的佳偶
She seems like a real prize.
的确
She is.
酒吧都关了  但看我拿到了什么好东西
Bar was already shut down, but look what I scored.
你好  卡洛琳
Hi, Caroline.
-你来干什么  -保罗在吗
- What do you want? - Is Paul around?
保罗  是你让他来的吗
Paul? Did you invite this man?
回答我  是你让他来的吗
Answer me. Did you invite him?
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
卡洛琳  别说了
Caroline, stop!
不  我就要说
No, you're not going to stop me.
保罗  有时间聊聊吗
Paul? You got a minute to talk?
没什么好聊的
There's nothing to talk about.
我想为上次在华盛顿的时候
I want to apologize for when I saw you last time
我的恶劣态度向你道歉
in Washington, how I treated you.
就这样吗
Is that it?
我还想和你谈谈船厂的事
And I want to talk about the shipyard.
我想到了补救的办法
I got a plan to fix it.
别把所有钱都放在个人退休账户里
You don't want everything going into the Roth IRA.
每年只要五千到一万
5, 10 grand a year,
我帮你做个多元化的好投资
I'll set you up with a nice, diversified package.
风险小  收益高
Low-risk, high-yield.
克莱尔和我能打理好
I think Claire and I have things pretty well under control.
如果连资深国会议员都投资我的基金
If I brought a senior U.S. Congressman into the fund,
那我在公司可就牛气多了
that would really up my stock in the company.
你们在那儿聊什么呢
What are you all gabbing about back there?
我们在聊老图书馆
We're talking about the old library.
是啊  要怎么处理它啊
Yeah, what's happening to it?
会拆掉吗
They gonna tear it down?
不知道
I don't know.
他们可以翻修这地方
They could gut it.
把它改造成学生活动中心
They could turn it into a student center.
我们溜进去吧
We should sneak in there.
就像以前那样
Like we used to.
-我参加  -就这么定了
- I'm game. - Do it.
何乐而不为呢
Hell, why not?
好了  就是这样  能进了
That's it. There you go. That's it.
安静点  这可是图书馆
Shh. It's a library.
这里可是桑蒂诺
This is the Sentinel...
造船厂协会存了三百万美元
The association had about 3 million saved up
以备不时之需
in reserve for emergencies.
平分给一万两千人  每人所得寥寥无几
Split that up between 12,000 members, it's nothing.
仅够几周的食品杂货
A couple of weeks' groceries.
我在忙一项法案
There's a bill I'm working on.
大笔联邦政府资金投入修建公园绿地
Major federal funds going towards public parks,
绿色商业空间  以及清理垃圾场
green commercial spaces, cleaning up waste sites.
那就有建设工程  公园管理  零售
That's construction jobs, park management, retail...
-能带来多少岗位  -五千个
- How many? - 5,000 jobs.
-都不到一半  -这是个开始
- That's not even half. - It's a start.
-要多久  -一年  或者两年
- How soon? - A year, maybe two.
要两年
Two fucking years?
在那之前我们该怎么办
What are we supposed to do until then?
听着  明天有一场社区会议
Listen, there's a community meeting tomorrow.
我听说了
I heard.
我会把一切都详细说明
I'm gonna go over everything in detail.
-你会出席吗  -没这个打算
- You gonna be there? - Wasn't planning on it.
我希望你能去
I'd like you to be there.
大家都尊敬你
Everybody respects you.
想让我为你做担保
Want me to vouch for you?
听着  告诉你一件事
Listen, I'm gonna tell you something that
只有少数几个人知道
only a handful of people know.
我要竞选州长
I'm running for governor.
不久就要宣布了
I announce soon.
但在此之前  我需要造船厂协会的支持
But I need the association behind me before I do that.
我知道  造船厂的事我让你们失望了
Now, I know I let you down with the shipyard.
但如果我成功当选州长
But if I win a governor's race,
我就能让一切重回正轨
I can get everything back on track.
你跑到我家来  求我原谅你
You show up on my doorstep asking for my forgiveness.
我都失业了  你想让我给你当宠物狗
Now you want me to be your lapdog after I lost my fucking job?
这份流域法案仅仅是个开始
This watershed bill is just the beginning.
如果我当上州长  我能做更多
If I'm governor, there's so much I can do.
都是胡说  你就是想利用我
It's bullshit. You just want to use me.
不是那样的
It's not like that.
就是这么回事
Yeah. It's exactly like that.
老天呐  彼得
Jesus Christ, Pete.
你们这群该死的政客
You fucking politicians.
保罗
Paul.
克莱尔
Claire.
没想到你和弗兰克也住这里
I didn't realize you and Frank were staying here.
每次来查尔斯顿我们都住这里
We always stay here when we're in Charleston.
你知道的  雷米
You know that, Remy.
08年竞选
The '08 campaign.
我发誓这纯属巧合
I promise it was a coincidence
是我助理订的
my assistant booked it.
弗兰克在吗
Is, uh, Frank around?
他不在  去和老同学狂欢了
He's not. He's off cavorting with old classmates.
过来坐下喝一杯吗
You want to sit down and have a drink?
他们给我订了蜜月套房
They booked me the bridal suite.
有冰镇香槟
There's champagne on ice.
天啊  自从离开了弗兰西斯
My, my, you've grown very confident
你变得很自信啊
since you worked for Francis.
我一直很自信  克莱尔
I've always been confident, Claire.
要是从前  你可绝不会邀我上楼
Oh, you never would have invited me upstairs.
以前没住过蜜月套房
Never had the bridal suite.
员工都住在四个街区外的
The staff always stayed in the Best Western
贝斯特韦斯特酒店
four blocks away.
好好享用你的香槟吧
Enjoy your champagne.
只是约你喝杯酒  绝没别的意思
I wasn't suggesting anything more than a drink.
是吗
Weren't you?
纯属礼貌之举
Purely being polite.
晚安  雷米
Good night, Remy.
蜜月套房在最顶层
The bridal suite's on the top floor
走廊的尽头
at the end of the hallway,
随时欢迎你
if you change your mind.
晚安  克莱尔
Good night, Claire.
山上有个姑娘*
*I know a girl upon a hill
穿着粉红衣裳*
*I know a girl all dressed in pink
-*她害得我*  -*满手味儿*
*- She made my... * *- Fingers stink
奏起军乐*
*Sound off, oo-wah
大声唱*
*Make it loud
三  四  到了
3, 4! Yeah!
过来吧
Here you go.
肯尼  我看你胖了一圈  钻不过来了
Hey, Kenny, I think you got a little too big for this.
是洞变小了
I think the hole got a lot smaller.
别让腰围阻挡你的脚步
Don't let a little girth stop you.
到了  快看  快看
Here it is. Look, look, look.
好家伙  你找到了
Oh, oh, you found it, killer.
快看
Oh, wow, look at that.
81届步枪兵  菲尔・兰登  弗兰克・安德伍德  蒂姆・科贝特肯・卡斯维尔
噢  仙纳度*
*Oh, Shenandoah
我多想听到你声音*
*I long to hear you
波涛翻滚  流向远方*
*Far away you rolling river
噢  仙纳度*
*Oh, Shenandoah
只求靠近你*
*Just to be near you
绵延向前*
*Far away
汹涌远去*
*Around the way
跨越广阔的密苏里*
*Cross the wide Missouri
很好  你呢
Good, and you?
其实我在查尔斯顿
Oh, I'm in Charleston, actually.
你怎么在这儿
What are you doing here?
我想给你个惊喜
I thought I'd surprise you.
惊喜吧
Surprise.
来  带你看看我青春期住的房间
Come on. Let me show you where I went through puberty.
我完全想象得出你16岁的样子
I can totally see you here at 16.
在这床上惹了不少麻烦吧
Got in some trouble on this bed, huh?
吵醒了整个街区
Woke up the whole block.
跟保罗谈得怎么样了
Hey, how'd it go with Paul?
他让我滚蛋
He told me to fuck off.
我妈也用她独有的方式
Which is what my mother told me,
表达了同样的意思
in her own special way.
我能去见她吗
Am I going to meet her?
你不会想见她的
You don't want to meet her.
我就想顺道拜访一下
I just wanted to stop by,
打声招呼  见个面
say hey, see her face.
克里斯蒂娜  你能来真好
Christina, it was really sweet of you to come up here.
说真的  我完全确定
Seriously, I'm officially convinced
你是我交往过的最好的女朋友
you're the most amazing woman I've ever been with,
但这次我是真心想自己解决这事
but I meant it when I said I wanted to take this trip alone.
明天肯定会闹得很不愉快
This thing tomorrow isn't going to be pleasant.
所以我才来  来支持你
Which is why I came... to be here for you.
精神支持
Moral support.
我了解这些人
I know these people.
他们不会给我好脸色的
They're going to lay into me big time.
明天对竞选很关键
Tomorrow's an important day for the campaign.
别跟我争
Don't fight me on this.
好吧
Okay.
我是住酒店呢
So do I get a hotel?
还是留在这儿
Do I stay here?
拜托  别这样嘛
Come on. Don't be like that.
酒店要舒服点
A hotel would be more comfortable.
不能浪费宝贵的竞选经费啊
But it would be a waste of valuable campaign funds.
竞选经费
Oh, campaign funds.
看到天花板上那条裂缝了吗
You see that crack up in the ceiling?
我以前每晚都盯着它入睡
I used to fall asleep staring at it every night.
每一寸  每个转折我都熟悉
I know every inch and curve.
这儿好黑  我好怕啊
It's dark in here. I'm scared.
小心点  兄弟
Be fucking careful, man!
亮起来
Let there be light!
你在想什么
What were you thinking about?
你和弗兰克为什么不要小孩
How come you and Frank have never had kids?
你也没有小孩
You've never had kids.
没错  但我没结婚
Yeah, but I'm not married.
回答我
Answer the question.
我们就是不想要
We just decided not to.
不是什么大事
There wasn't some big conversation.
你在说谎
I think you're lying.
随你怎么想
Think whatever you want.
你真的没考虑过
You've honestly never thought about it?
也许想过一两次吧
I mean, yeah, maybe, once or twice.
我并不觉得少了什么
I mean, I don't feel there's some void.
没有孩子我也很开心
I'm perfectly happy without.
你呢
What about you?
你能想象我为婴儿擦屁股  换尿布吗
Can you imagine me wiping a baby's ass and changing nappies?
不能
No, I can't.
其实  我刚刚想了
Actually, yes, I just did.
我要挂电话了
I'm gonna have to get off the phone.
你破坏了气氛
You've ruined everything.
我们确实该挂了
Well, we really should get off.
都一个多小时了吧
It's been... over an hour, I think.
好
Okay.
-你挂吧  -我马上就挂
- Go on then. - I'm hanging up right now.
不  我先挂
No, I am.
加油  别放弃
Come on. Don't quit on me.
我忘记做了几个了
Oh, I lost count.
别  别放弃
Don't be... don't quit.
天啊
Oh... oh, God!
你赢了
Oh, you win.
但这不是公平竞争
Oh, but it's not a fair fight.
你开了家漂流公司
You run a rafting company.
而我整天坐在办公室里
I sit behind a desk all day.
我倒想看看你拿着划桨
Oh, I'd love to see your ass with a paddle,
在四级急流里上蹿下跳
bouncing through a class-four rapid.
我能让国会俯首称臣
If I can whip congress into submission,
就不怕那点浪花
I'm not afraid of a little white water.
你无法驯服急流  弗兰克
You can't tame a rapid, Frank.
我心脏跳得好快
My heart is beating so fast...
如果我心脏病发  就是你的错
If I have a heart attack, it's your fault.
我也跳很快
Mine too.
来
Here.
我得再喝一杯
I need another drink.
我也是
I think I'll have another too.
别一人独享
Don't bogart that.
你觉得是这里造就了我们吗
Do you think this place made us?
什么意思
How do you mean?
我今天在校园里走
When I walked on campus today,
不禁在想  这地方有意义吗
I wondered, "Did it mean anything?
只是我们度过四年时光的地方
"If it's just a place we spent four years of our lives...
还是有别的意义
or was there more?"
我不知道
I don't know.
但我一直知道  终有一天
I do know you were always the guy
会有栋楼以你的名字命名
that was gonna get a building named after him.
我们都是小屁孩
I knew that the moment I saw you
你却能骂走教官  那时我就知道
cuss out the drill sergeant when we were knobs.
图书馆是个幌子
The library is a sham.
希金斯要我帮个忙
Higgins asked me a favor.
我让别人帮个忙
I asked someone else a favor.
他们就把我名字放了上去
They slapped my name on it.
和其他事一样  只是政治
Politics. Like everything else.
不是所有人都会被请去帮忙
Not everybody gets asked those favors.
也不是所有人都帮得上
Or knows how to deliver on 'em.
五十年后  那里也会被别的建筑取代
Oh, in 50 years they'll just replace it with something else.
就像这里被我的楼取代
Just like they're doing with this for mine.
你还是造过栋楼  不论它能维持多久
You still built something. However long it lasts.
图书馆没什么要紧
The library doesn't matter.
但我希望这里有些意义
But I want to think this place did.
它对那时的我们意义重大
I think it meant a lot to us. Then.
那我们呢
And what about us?
说实话  我没想过那么多
Honestly, I haven't really thought about it that much.
很久以前的事了
It's a long time ago.
我们以前那么好
We were so close.
像兄弟
Like brothers.
不止兄弟
More than brothers.
我们当时还小  弗兰克
We were kids, Frank.
闯过几次祸
We messed around a couple of times.
我被你深深吸引
I was so drawn to you.
我总能让你开怀大笑
I could always make you laugh.
我们怎么断了联络呢
How did we lose touch?
你上了法学院  我去当兵了
You went to law school. I joined the army.
你竞选议员  我搬去了科罗拉多
You ran for congress, I... I moved to Colorado.
三十年过去了
30 years goes by.
我的孩子都比那时的我们大了
I got children older than we were back then.
你有孩子吗  弗兰克
Do you have anyone, Frank?
我有克莱尔
I have Claire.
除了克莱尔呢
Besides Claire.
时不时会有
I have. From time to time.
我想要谁就是谁
If I want someone, I want them.
魅力使然
It's attraction.
能让你开心我也开心  弗兰克
Made me happy to make you happy, Frank.
没什么不好的
Didn't see any harm in it.
你知道我为什么喜欢漂流吗
You know why I love rafting?
在水上漂流时
When you're on the water,
你能想的只有眼前的事
all you're thinking about is what's right in front of you.
一切尽在这一瞬
Everything is in the moment.
真没时间回想过去
I don't really have time to think about the past.
我很在乎你
You meant something to me.
我深信不疑
I believe that.
喝光啦
All gone.
我不太舒服
I don't feel so well.
要吐了吗
You gonna be sick?
不是  我只想...
No. No, I just...
休息一下
take a break.
我们休息...
Can we just take a...
一下  好吗
for a little bit?
让我缓缓
Until I feel better.
安心休息吧
Take as long as you like.
我哪都不去
I got nowhere to go.
克莱尔  来电
都快七点了
It's almost 7:00.
我没打算睡着的
I don't even wanna sleep.
起来吧
Come on.
一...二...三...四...
One... Two... Three... Four...
一二三四
One, two, three, four,
我们是桑蒂诺
we are the Sentinel.
-已开发1100英亩土地  -是的
- 1,100 acres are developed. - Yes.
-30%是公园  -是的
- 30% public parks. - Yep.
-45%是购物区  -是的
- 45% shopping offices. - Yes.
25%是中等收入家庭住房
25% middle-income housing.
你去吗
You going?
非得去吗
Is it required?
好像不是
I don't think so.
冠名图书馆的人是谁
Who is he that they're naming the place after?
在这儿上过学的家伙  好像已经死了
Some guy who went here. I think he's dead.
昨天非要我们布置椅子
We had to set up the chairs yesterday.
热死人了
It was hot as shit.
真不爽
That sucks.
典礼开始前我想先去打个盹
I'm gonna try to get some shut-eye before the ceremony.
-待会儿见  -回头见
- I'll see you all later? - Later it is.
弗兰克  趁我还记得  这是我的名片
Frank, before I forget, here's my card.
让你的经理人跟我联系
So your money manager can call me.
去休息吧
Get some rest.
克莱尔
Claire.
你看起来很难受
You look like you're hurting.
我们闹了个通宵
It was an all-nighter.
-总归有些乐子吧  -很有意思
- Was it fun at least? - It was fun.
我得去打个盹
I need to get some shut-eye.
雷米也在这儿
Remy's staying here.
他为捐款的事来烦你了吗
He harassing you about the donations?
我应付得来
Oh, nothing I can't handle.
快去休息吧
Go get some rest.
球队球员  其中有罗素
-你厉害吗  -还不算差
- Were you good? - Not bad.
我不是先发球员
I mean, I wasn't a starter,
但也打了挺长时间
but I got my time on the court.
我觉得你长开之后更性感
I think you look sexier now all grown up.
议员先生  我们准备就绪了
Congressman? We're ready for you.
请勿打扰
你说两年时间
You said two years.
我认为两年是比较实际的估计
I think two years is a realistic estimate.
还是在法案通过的情况下
If it passes at all.
我认为能通过
Which I think it will.
你认为还是能确定
You think or you know?
我不敢百分百保证  但我有信心它会通过
I can't predict 100%, but I'm confident it will.
你认为  你有信心
You think, you're confident,
你不能百分百保证
you can't predict 100%.
对我们有什么用
How does any of that help us?
我跟你说
I'll tell you something.
我现在百分百无力还贷
I am 100% unable to pay my mortgage right now.
百分百没钱给孩子购买学习用品
I'm 100% unable to buy my kids school supplies.
你要我们靠我丈夫的残疾人补贴生活吗
We supposed to live off my husband's disability?
我们会开展带薪培训项目
There'll be paid training programs available.
他们会付多少钱
How much will they pay?
我承认  比在造船厂赚的少
Uh, granted, it's less than you made at the shipyard.
-那是多少  -每小时6美元
- So how much? - It's about $6 an hour.
那都达不到最低工资标准
That's not even minimum wage.
你要把它看做一笔投资
You have to see it as an investment.
培训计划是很有价值的资源
The training programs are a valuable resource.
你休想
You're not getting it.
我无力做投资
I can't afford to make investments.
6美元一小时我全家都要睡马路了
Six dollars an hour puts my family on the street.
你想让我怎么样  做五份兼职吗
What do you want me to work? Five jobs?
如果你找一份兼职  再加上培训计划
If you get a part-time job, that and the training programs...
你知道我是怎么想的吗
Do you wanna know what I think?
我觉得你整天在华盛顿无所事事
I think you sit around in Washington
想出一些在文件中看上去很好的
coming up with all sorts of fancy numbers and solutions
数据和解决方案
that look good on paper.
对我们来说却根本不适用
But that doesn't cut it for the rest of us.
你说你会照顾我们  你这个骗子
You said you had our backs, you lying piece of shit!
那些文件不能填饱肚子
We don't eat paper for dinner.
也不能用来遮风避雨
You can't put a paper roof over your head.
我们为你投票的时候
When we all voted for you,
我们都没有想到自己是在
I didn't think that every one of those votes
自掘坟墓
was another nail in our own coffin.
大家稍坐十分钟
Everybody just sit down for ten minutes.
我们可以逐条讨论这份提议
We can go over this proposal point by point
你们可以获知一切关于
and you can get the information that you need
你们所需资源的信息
to get the resources that you want.
就好像他们根本不想要解决方案
It's like they don't want to find a solution.
他们害怕了
They're scared.
我知道他们害怕了
I understand that they're scared,
但也不代表他们不能听取建议
but that doesn't mean they can't listen.
你不了解这些人  克里斯蒂娜
You don't know these people, Christina.
我在你的办公室工作了三年
I worked in your office for three years.
我和他们谈过话  我接过他们的电话
I spoke to them. I took their calls.
我回过他们的电子邮件
I replied to their emails.
可你没跟他们一起长大
You didn't grow up with them.
我不需要和他们一起长大
I don't need to grow up hand to mouth
来同情现状...
to empathize with the fact that...
他们不需要同情
they're not interested in empathy.
房子钥匙在我外套里
The house keys are in my jacket.
我回头打给你
I'll call you.
-彼得  -我说了我回头打给你
- Peter. - I said I'll call you.
做好功课  答案是玛丽・约瑟修女
Do your homework. It's Sister Mary Joseph.
不是你做的  别对我撒谎
You didn't do it. Don't lie to me.
我以前也是这么对付我父母的
I used to use the same ploy with my parents.
胡扯
Nah, baloney.
我们先做功课  然后吃饭
We do the homework and then we eat.
好了  谁饿了
All right, who's hungry?
-你们想吃什么  -汉堡
- What do you guys want? - Hamburgers.
妈妈要做奶酪空心粉...
You know mommy makes macaroni...
不  要吃披萨
No, pizza.
不行  你们每顿饭都吃那个
No pizza. You guys can eat that every...
亲爱的  带孩子们上楼
sweetheart, take the kids upstairs.
你怎么进来的
How'd you get in here?
你还是把备用钥匙
You still keep the spare key
藏在门廊那块松动的砖头后面
behind the loose brick on the porch.
你闯进我家
You break into my house?
你这样吓唬我的孩子
You scare my kids like that?
我们得谈谈  保罗
We gotta talk, Paul.
我们昨晚谈过了  现在滚出去
We talked last night. Now get out.
我能说服这些人  但我需要你的帮助
I can convince these people, but I need your help.
-滚出我家  -坐下
- Leave my house. - Sit down.
我孩子就在楼上我不想伤你  彼得
I don't wanna have to hurt you with my children upstairs, Petey.
那就帮帮我
Then help me.
这是你最后的机会
This is your last chance.
我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
回楼上去
Get back upstairs!
我们这是在干什么
What are we doing?
我不想打你  彼得
I don't wanna fight you, Petey.
我也不想打你
I don't wanna fight you either.
我会这么做
I will.
但我们没必要这样
But we don't have to.
你想让我做什么
What do you want me to do?
你们选举我代表你
You elected me to represent you,
但我不能阻止不可避免的事
but I couldn't forestall the inevitable.
造船厂注定得关闭
The shipyard was closing.
不在今年  就是明年
If not this year, then next.
或是后年
Or the year after.
我们都清楚
We all know that.
我可以对你们撒谎
I could have lied to you.
我可以假装忙活一阵
I could have pretended to do more.
但我不相信活在过去
But I don't believe about living in the past.
我只在乎未来
I only care about the future.
还有一个你们很难接受的事实
Here's another truth that's gonna be hard to swallow.
你们只有我了
I'm all you've got.
华盛顿没有人在乎你们
Nobody in Washington gives a fuck about you.
没有人
No one.
他说的没错
He's right.
不管你们怎么看彼得
Whatever you think of Petey,
我们就只有他给的这一条路
we either go with him or we got nothin'.
我的提议
Now, does what I'm offering you
的确距你们想要的  应得的差得很远
come anywhere near what you want or deserve? No.
但你们要打开眼界  着眼当前
But you gotta open your eyes and take what's in front of you.
这是一个基础
We can build on that.
五千个工作岗位变成一万个
5,000 jobs becomes 10,000.
然后变成一万五千个  的确要等一段时间
Then 15,000. Not in the snap of a finger,
但绝对比停滞不前快
but faster than doing nothing will.
我能指望你们大伙吗
Can I count on all of you?
好的  我就当你们默许了
All right, I'll take that as a yes.
请留下你们的联系方式
We'll need your contact information
好给你们寄去材料和你们的朋友分享
so we can send you materials to share with your friends.
现在来说一下
Now, let's talk about the way
资金分阶段引入的方式
the money's gonna get phased in.
钱分六步到位  第一步
It's gonna happen in six stages. Stage one...
你看那星条旗*
*Oh say does that star-spangled
是否还依旧飘扬*
*Banner yet wave
在这自由的国度*
*For the land of the free
勇士的家乡*
*And the home of the brave
向左转  齐步走
Left face. Forward march.
弗兰西斯・安德伍德的职业生涯
Francis Underwood's career.
哈佛法学学位
Harvard law degree.
南卡罗莱纳州史上最年轻的州议员之一
One of the youngest state legislators in the history of South Carolina.
在美国国会干了22年的老兵
A 22-year veteran of the U.S. Congress.
众议院多数党党鞭
House majority whip.
是年轻人在桑蒂诺所学价值观的
Speaks volumes about the values young people learn here
最佳表率
at the Sentinel.
荣誉  责任  纪律
Values like honor, duty, discipline,
牺牲  服务和尊重
like sacrifice, service, and respect.
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
弗兰西斯・J・安德伍德图书馆
the Francis J. Underwood library.
议员先生
Congressman?
谢谢
Thank you.
我写了一份发言稿
I wrote a speech.
但我不打算读了
But I'm not gonna read it.
没有什么是永恒的  即使是我身后的建筑
Nothing is permanent. Not even this building.
我不是不领情
I don't mean to sound ungrateful.
我很感激  我非常荣幸
I am very grateful. I'm deeply honored.
而且
And I am...
非常感动
I'm very moved.
我有幸和几位好朋友一起度过了
I had the good fortune of spending most of this weekend
这个周末
with a group of friends.
很长时间没有见面的好朋友
Friends I haven't seen in a very long time.
我在这里交到的朋友
Friends I made here.
你们大部分年轻学员可能不知道我是谁
Most of you young cadets probably, uh, don't know who I am.
一位政客  一个名字  有些成就
A politician, a name, a few accomplishments.
但我不怪你们
But I don't blame you.
我像你们这么大的时候
When I was your age,
我也不在意那些灰发人做了什么
why, I didn't care much for what men in gray hair did
说了什么
or what they had to say.
我
I...
我真不知怎么说...
I wish I could describe...
和谐  这就是一直萦绕在我脑海的词
Harmony. That's the word that stuck in my mind.
和谐
Harmony.
与持久或永恒无关
It's not about what's lasting or permanent.
而是不同的声音  汇集在一起
It is about individual voices coming together.
只有那一瞬
For a moment.
那个瞬间
And that moment lasts...
只有一息之长
the length of a breath.
这就是我对自己在这里的那段时光的看法
That's what I think about my time here.
请你们原谅我
You'll have to forgive me.
我昨晚多喝了几杯威士忌
I had more than a few whiskeys last night.
我还是个学员的时候  我们可以通宵畅饮
You know, when I was a cadet, we could drink all night
早上起来还能行军20英里
and then get up in the morning and march 20 Miles,
但现在我能上这三步台阶都算幸运
but these days I'm lucky I got up these three steps.
我想感谢大家
I wanna thank you very much.
这是莫大的荣幸
This is a great honor.
我想感谢希金斯校长
I wanna thank president Higgins
当然还有我一生的挚爱  克莱尔
and of course the love of my life, Claire.
非常感谢你们
Thank you all very much.
-你还好吗  -嗯
- You okay? - Yes.
妈
Hi, ma.
这是克里斯蒂娜  昨天和你提过她
This is Christina. I told you about her yesterday.
-你好  罗素太太  -嗯
- Hi, Mrs. Russo. - Hey.
我们是来道别的
We just came by to say goodbye.
-我们要赶一小时后的火车  -好
- We have to catch a train in about an hour. - Okay.
-还没人来修灯吗  -没有
- They still haven't fixed that light? - Uh-uh.
今天很顺利
Things went well today.
我想我得到造船厂伙计们的支持了
I think the folks in the yard are gonna get behind me.
彼得做得很棒
Peter did a great job.
把那条毯子给我
Hand me that blanket.
这里的空调能冻死人
The A.C. in here is nuts.
你的手怎么了
What happened to your hand?
我打了一架
I got in a fight.
你赢了吗
Did you win?
嗯  我想是的
Yeah, I guess I did.
这才是我的彼得
That's my Peter.
你在上我儿子啊
So you're fucking my son.
别紧张  和你开玩笑的
Lighten up. I'm just messing with you.
打扰
Excuse me.
稍等  有事吗
Yeah. Hold on a second. Yeah?
我妈住409房
Yeah, my mother's in room 409.
她房间的灯坏了  需要更换
She has a light out that needs to be replaced.
好的  我知道了
All right. I'll take care of it.
好  谢谢
Okay, thanks.
听着  宝贝  如果你穿上粉色那件
Look, babe, if you put that pink thing on,
我跟你说
I'm telling you...
等等  又怎么了
Hold on. What is it?
我妈妈房间里的灯
The light in my mother's room.
我说了过会儿会去看的
I told you I'll take care of it later.
不行  你现在就得搞定
No, you'll take care of it now.
我得挂了
I gotta go.
顺便关了空调
And turn the A.C. down while you're in there too.
知道了  先生
Yes, sir.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
不客气  先生
You're very welcome, sir.
你要保重
You take care of yourself.
我真为你骄傲  弗兰克
I'm real proud of you, Frank.
虽然不想承认  但我也是
I hate to admit it, but I feel the same.
你们的出席  让今天意义非凡
Well, having all you here was what made it special.
有空常联系
Now you stay in touch.
-一定  -再见  兄弟
- Will do. - See ya, buddy.
典礼很棒  弗兰克
Beautiful ceremony, Frank.
是啊  他们干得不错
Yeah, they did a good job.
你的演讲  我很高兴今天来了
Your speech. I'm glad I was here for that.
我也是
Me too.
你该抽空来萨里达看看
You should come out to Salida sometime.
我带你去游览阿肯色河
I'll take you out on the Arkansas river.
-我是该去看看  -随时欢迎
- I should do that. - Any time you want.
好
Yep.
All right.
弗兰西斯
Francis?
艾德华备好车了
Edward has the car ready.
我马上过去
I'll be right there.
不着急
Take your time.
彼得那儿情况如何
You hear from Peter?
似乎造船厂的员工同意了
Looks like the shipbuilders are on board.
明早我们就着手草拟
Tomorrow morning we start working on his draft
-他的竞选声明  -好的
- for his announcement speech. - Got it.
我还要看一下流域法案模型的简报
And I want the brief on the mock-up for the watershed bill.
我带着呢
I got that with me.
乘我的车去机场
Ride with me to the airport.
我们路上说
We'll go through it in the car.
翻译  waterlike
翻译  ~某人
翻译  小蟹
翻译  猪猪
翻译  泽川
翻译  sakura
翻译  天意
时间轴  吉吉
顾问  老杜
后期  饿得慌
校对  草草
总监  草草
纸牌屋
第一季  第八集
人人影视倾情奉献